

Marco Abel Zefanya

Jakarta Selatan | 081294150023 | marcoabel25@gmail.com

About Me

I'm Marco Abel Zefanya graduated from Gunadarma University with a bachelor's degree in engineering, worked as a Quality Assurance Engineer, to ensuring high quality standard code for automatic cars transmission systems for 2 years. I have a good communication skill, able to work in team and under pressure, have great problem solving, attention to detail. I am very interested in Web Development field, especially back-end.

Personal Skill

- HTML / CSS / Bootstrap
- PHP
- MySQL
- JavaScript
- Golang
- C
- Version Control System (Git)
- Teamwork
- Leadership Skill
- · Time Management
- Adaptive
- Problem Solving

Work Experience

PT SYS Indonesia

Software Quality Assurance (Sept 2021 - Nov 2023)

White Box testing for automotive transmissions, which requires a deep proficiency in the C programming language, using winAMS tools, and excel formulas.

Quality Assurance of BMW and FIAT Project

We are as a team doing white box testing for automatic transmission for BWM, and FIAT car. We must reach 100% precentage from Coverage Testing, find and fixing the bugs, and make reporting file to QA Lead.

Quality Assurance of A Spice/Volkswagen Project

- Analyze data and review the requirements needed to test a product
- · Make plans for detailed tests, test cases based on the source code
- Conduct testing with the unit testing method · Finding and fixing bugs in the source code
- Preparing test result report to the QA Lead

PART TIME - PT KAI

Data Entry PT KAI Expo (2017 - 2018)

Collecting data from all customers, grouping by their destination, and double checking to customers about their ticket before inserting the data into database.

Organization & Volunteer Expriences

ASIAN PARA GAMES 2018 Main Gate Ticketing Supervisor

Monitoring and handling the crowded at Main Gate Ticketing Supervisor in **Gelora Bung Karno** Gate 5

ASIAN GAMES JAKARTA PALEMBANG 2018 Main Gate Ticketing Supervisor

Monitoring and handling the crowded at Main Gate Ticketing Supervisor in

Gelora Bung Karno Gate 5

Education History Gunadarma University

Bachelor of Informatic Engineering - GPA 3.21/4.00 Senior High School

· Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint

2013 - 2016

2016 - 2020

SMA Bakti Idhata

- **Tools Skill**
- Postman
- Figma Katalon
- winAMS

Find me on:



Marco Abel Zefanya



Visual Studio Code, Notepad ++